adbrands.net 2002-12-04

# Adbrands.net: Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

This page describes the Privacy Policy of the Adbrands.net website.

**Information Automatically Logged  **

The Adbrands.net web server automatically collects information about which pages are visited and the IP address or domain name of visitors, and information about where the user has come from. We use this data to ensure that the site's contents are relevant to users, for internal review and for audits of visitor traffic. We do not hold any information that personally identifies any visitor. Usage logs are periodically deleted. 

**Cookies**

Adbrands.net's internal ad server uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use an outside ad company, Burst Media, to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies, which are collected by our ad company. We do not have access to this information. Burst Media have a separate privacy policy which is available [here](https://www.burstmedia.com/release/privacy.asp). 

**Registration Forms**

The subscriber registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal code) and unique identifiers (like a username and password). Contact information is used if we need to get in touch with customers. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Unique identifiers are collected from subscribers to verify their identity when logging into the system. The financial information (for example credit card details) that is collected on the registration form is held within the secure server of our transaction agents, Netbanx Ltd, part of the [NetInvest Group](http://www.netinvest.co.uk/). We do not have access to this information, we will not renew subscriptions without the specific instruction of each subscriber. 

**External Links  **

This site contains links to other sites. Adbrands.net is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Public Forums  **

Adbrands.net also manages a separate free mailing list and discussion forum, hosted at Yahoo Groups. Paid subscribers to Adbrands.net are automatically added to the mailing list. Other Adbrands.net users may choose to sign up to the service. Members of the mailing list will receive periodic announcements from Adbrands.net and possibly from other Adbrands.net users and subscribers. All announcements are moderated. However, please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. You may remove yourself from this list at any time by sending an email to  [adbrands](mailto:adbrands-unsubscribe@yahoogroups.com)[-unsubscribe@yahoogroups.com](mailto:adbrands-unsubscribe@yahoogroups.com). This mailing list is not available to third parties, and only the forum moderator has access to the directory of members. Yahoo Groups.com has a separate privacy policy which is available [here](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/).

* * *

_Adbrands.net. All rights reserved © Mind Advertising Ltd 1998-2002_
